Guide to the David Tibet Current 93 archive, 1960s-circa 2013.
Tibet, David Current 93 archive
- Series VI. Audio/Visual Material
  - Subseries VI a. CDs (David Tibet Groups)
    - Nurse With Wound, CD-3216 (Box 12)
      The Swinging Reflective
    - Antony and Current 93, CD-3219 (Box 12)
      PanDurtro 007
  - Subseries VI b. CDs (Other)
    Organized alphabetically by artist
    - 150 Murderous Passions, CD-3085 (Box 10, Box D)
      151 Murderous Passions
    - 23 Skidoo, CD-3086 (Box 10, Box D)
      The Culling is Coming
    - Aethenor, CD-3087 (Box 10, Box D)
      Faking Gold and Murder
    - Aleister Crowley, CD-3088 (Box 10, Box D)
      Aleister Crowley
    - ALU, CD-3089 (Box 10, Box D)
      Autismenschen
    - Aneamn, CD-3090 (Box 10, Box D)
    - Anna Colitti, CD-3091 (Box 10, Box D)
    - Aranos, CD-3092 (Box 10, Box D)
      Transfixiatio
    - Backworld, CD-3093 (Box 10, Box D)
      Anthems from the Pleasure Park
    - Backworld, CD-3094 (Box 10, Box D)
      Come the Bells
    - Backworld, CD-3095 (Box 10, Box D)
      Of Silver Sleep
    - Backworld, CD-3096 (Box 10, Box D)
      Seeds of Love
    - Backworld, CD-3097 (Box 10, Box D)
      The Orchids
    - Batan Lewis Sanders, CD-3098 (Box 10, Box D)
      The Inner Demon demos
    - Black Ships, CD-3099 (Box 10, Box D)
      Black Ship Time
    - Black Sun Productions, CD-3100 (Box 10, Box D)
      Im Gegenteil
    - Blood Axis, CD-3101 (Box 10, Box D)
      Born Again
    - Calliope Tsoupaki, CD-3218 (Box 12)
      Medea
    - Centre for Open Education, CD-3102 (Box 11, Box E)
      AHPG856: Lectures
    - Chalk, Andrew, CD-3104 (Box 11, Box E)
      This Growing Clearing
    - Chalk, Andrew, CD-3105 (Box 11, Box E)
      Over the Edge
    - Chalk, Andrew, CD-3103 (Box 12)
      The Days After
    - Chris Connelly, CD-3106 (Box 11, Box E)
      Day of Knowledge
    - Coil, CD-3107-3108 (Box 11, Box E)
      The Golden Hare with a Voice of Silver
    - Coil, CD-3109 (Box 11, Box E)
      Panic
    - Coil, CD-3110 (Box 11, Box E)
      Steve, Pay Us What You Owe Us!
    - Coil, CD-3111 (Box 11, Box E)
      Unnatural History II
    - Comets on Fire, CD-3112 (Box 11, Box E)
      Comets on Fire
    - Comus, CD-3113 (Box 11, Box E)
      Cast of Sweden
    - Corridor, CD-3114 (Box 11, Box E)
      Corridor
    - Death in June, CD-3115-3116 (Box 11, Box E)
      Cathedral of Tears
    - August dErleth, CD-3117 (Box 11, Box E)
      Early Pioneers of the Miskatronic Workshop Vol. I
    - Bob Dylan, CD-3118 (Box 11, Box E)
      Discover Brokent
    - Earthling Tempel, CD-3119 (Box 11, Box E)
      Pilgramage to Thunderbolt Pagoda
    - Clara Engel, CD-3120 (Box 11, Box E)
      Secret Beasts
    - The Final Solstice, CD-3121 (Box 11, Box E)
      The Final Solstice II
    - The Floating World, CD-3122 (Box 11, Box E)
      The Floating World
    - Forms of Things Unknown, CD-3123 (Box 11, Box E)
      Cross Purposes
    - Francisco Lopez, CD-3124 (Box 11, Box E)
      United #275
    - Fursaxa, CD-3125 (Box 11, Box E)
      Live on Idiot control
    - Gonzo, CD-3126 (Box 11, Box E)
      Mind the Gap 63
    - The Goslings, CD-3127 (Box 11, Box E)
      Full Hunters Moon
    - Guru Guru; Uli Trepte, CD-3128 (Box 11, Box E)
      Hot on Spot/Inbetween
    - Heemann, CD-3129 (Box 11, Box E)
      Time is the Simplest Thing
    - H.N.A.S.; Mieses Gegonge, CD-3130 (Box 11, Box E)
      Abwassermusik
    - Hush Arbor, CD-3131 (Box 11, Box E)
      Yankee Reality
    - In Gowan Ring, CD-3132 (Box 11, Box E)
      In Gowan Ring
    - irr.app. (ext.), CD-3133, 3137 (Box 11, Box E)
      Dust Pincher Appliances
    - irr.app. (ext.), CD-3134 (Box 11, Box E)
      Foreign Matter, Nor Frequency Carrier
    - irr.app. (ext.), CD-3135 (Box 11, Box E)
      Inception and Silence Undivided
    - irr.app. (ext.), CD-3136 (Box 11, Box E)
      Their Little Bones...
    - irr.app. (ext.), CD-3215 (Box 12)
      Radiant Black Future
    - Julia Kent, CD-3138 (Box 11, Box E)
      Delay
    - Khan of Finland, CD-3139 (Box 11, Box E)
      Khan of Finland demo
    - Kinit Her, CD-3140 (Box 11, Box E)
      Glyms or Beame of Radicall Truthes
    - Kloster, CD-3141 (Box 11, Box E)
      Do Not Be Afraid
    - Lady Eleanore, CD-3142 (Box 11, Box E)
      Inactive Spring
    - The Legendary Pink Dots, CD-3143-3144 (Box 11, Box E)
      Chemical Playschool, 3 and 4
    - The Legendary Pink Dots, CD-3145 (Box 11, Box E)
      Shadow Weaver
    - The Legendary Pink Dots, CD-3146 (Box 11, Box E)
      Shadow Weaver II
    - Lemon Kittens, CD-3147 (Box 11, Box E)
      …The Big Dentist
    - Liturgy, CD-3148 (Box 11, Box E)
      Aesthethica
    - Magick Lantern Cycle, CD-3149 (Box 11, Box E)
      Chimaera
    - Marc Almond, CD-3150 (Box 11, Box E)
      Stardom Road
    - Marc Almond, CD-3207 (Box 12)
      The End of New York
    - Mirror, CD-3151 (Box 11, Box E)
      A Pilgrims Solace
    - Mirror, CD-3152 (Box 11, Box E)
      Die Spiegel Manufaktur
    - Mirror, CD-3153 (Box 11, Box E)
      Eye of the Storm
    - Mirror, CD-3154 (Box 11, Box E)
      In to the Wood
    - Mirror, CD-3155 (Box 11, Box F)
      The View
    - Monos, CD-3156 (Box 11, Box F)
      Monos
    - Nature and Organisation, CD-3157 (Box 11, Box F)
      A Dozen Summers against the World
    - Nature and Organisation, CD-3158 (Box 11, Box F)
      Beauty Reaps the Blood of Solitude
    - Nature and Organisation, CD-3159 (Box 11, Box F)
      Death in a Snow Leopard Winter
    - The Nodding Folk, CD-3220 (Box 12)
      The Nodding Folk
    - The North Sea, CD-3160 (Box 11, Box F)
      The North Sea
    - Operating Theatre, CD-3161 (Box 11, Box F)
      Rapid Eye Movements
    - Pantaleimon, CD-3162 (Box 11, Box F)
      Tall Trees
    - Pantaleimon, CD-3163 (Box 11, Box F)
      Firewalk
    - Pantaleimon, CD-3164-3165 (Box 11, Box F)
      Trees Sold Time
    - Poison Idea, CD-3166 (Box 11, Box F)
      Feel the Darkness
    - R.B. Russell, CD-3167 (Box 11, Box F)
      Ghosts
    - Boyd Rice, CD-3168 (Box 11, Box F)
      The Way I Feel
    - Rio en Medio, CD-3169 (Box 11, Box F)
      Frontier
    - Robert Aiki, CD-3170 (Box 11, Box F)
      Robert Aiki
    - Diana Rogerson and Andrew Liles, CD-3171 (Box 11, Box F)
      No Birds Do Song
    - ROTOR0006, CD-3172 (Box 11, Box F)
      Golem
    - Ruby Throat, CD-3211 (Box 12)
      O' Doubt O' Stars
    - Ruby Throat, CD-3212 (Box 12)
      Out of a Black Cloud Comes a Bird
    - Ruby Throat, CD-3213 (Box 12)
      The Ventriloquist
    - Sailors with Wax Wings, CD-3214 (Box 12)
      Sailors with Wax Wings
    - Chrystal Belle Scrodd, CD-3173 (Box 11, Box F)
      Beastings
    - Seven Year Rabbit Cycle, CD-3174 (Box 11, Box F)
      Ache Hornes
    - Simon Finn, CD-3175 (Box 11, Box F)
      Silent City Creep
    - Simon Finn, CD-3176 (Box 11, Box F)
      Subjunctive Mood
    - Six Organs of Admittance, CD-3177 (Box 11, Box F)
      The Manifestation
    - Slowlight, CD-3178 (Box 11, Box F)
      The Psychic Devotional
    - Slumberwood, CD-3179 (Box 11, Box F)
      Yowling Night Songs
    - SOL, CD-3180 (Box 11, Box F)
      Invictux-Lex Talionis
    - SOL, CD-3181 (Box 11, Box F)
      Offer thy Flesh to the Worms
    - Spectral Light and Moonshine, CD-3182 (Box 11, Box F)
      Firefly Snakeoil Jamboree
    - The Sonic Catering Band, CD-3183 (Box 11, Box F)
      Artificial Additives
    - Sorrow, CD-3184 (Box 11, Box F)
      Sleep Now Forever
    - Stereolab, CD-3185 (Box 11, Box F)
      Refried Extoplasm
    - Stone Breath, CD-3186 (Box 11, Box F)
      The Silver Skein Unwound
    - Stone Breath, CD-3187 (Box 11, Box F)
      A Silver Thread to Weave the Seasons
    - Stone Breath, CD-3188 (Box 11, Box F)
      Revelation Moon
    - Theory of Abstract Light, CD-3189 (Box 11, Box F)
      Theory of Abstract Light
    - Three Owls, Six Ears, CD-3190 (Box 11, Box F)
      Three Owls, Six Ears
    - Timothy Holehouse, CD-3191 (Box 11, Box F)
      In Search of the Binary Star
    - Trembling Bells, CD-3192 (Box 11, Box F)
      The Constant Pageant
    - Urthona, CD-3193 (Box 11, Box F)
      Super Heavy Hamoazian Reverie
    - Urthona, CD-3194 (Box 11, Box F)
      Amid Devonia's Alps
    - Unicazurn, CD-3195 (Box 11, Box F)
      Propeller Guru
    - Undecided, CD-3196 (Box 11, Box F)
      Undecided
    - Various Artists, CD-3197 (Box 11, Box F)
      Ohrenschrauben/Ohrensausen
    - Various Artists, CD-3198-3199 (Box 11, Box F)
      Brain in the Wire
    - Various Artists, CD-3208 (Box 12)
      MMp
    - Volcano the Bear, CD-3200 (Box 11, Box F)
      Five Hundred Boy Piano
    - Wakeford-Stapleton, CD-3201 (Box 11, Box F)
      Revenge of the Selfish Shellfish
    - Whitehouse, CD-3202 (Box 11, Box F)
      Cruise
    - David Wileman, CD-3203 (Box 11, Box F)
      Folkus
    - William Basinksi, CD-3204 (Box 11, Box F)
      Variations: A Movement in Chrome Primitive
    - Pepe Wismeer, CD-3205 (Box 11, Box F)
      Between Sheep and Pigs
    - Robert Wyatt, CD-3206 (Box 11, Box F)
      Comicopera
    - Xiu Xiu, CD-3217 (Box 12)
      Fag Patrol
    - Coptology Articles on DVDR, CD-3221 (Box 12)
    - OM GAMH, CD-3222 (Box 12)
    - Wildwood Rough Mixel, CD-3223 (Box 12)
    - 5 illegible CDS, 4 with duct-tape cases, CD-3224-3228 (Box 12)
    - OM, CD-3229 (Box 12)
      Bedouins Vigil
    - Hobatopbi Abahtabaa Okeah, CD-3230 (Box 12)
    - Codex Alimentarius, CD-3231 (Box 12)
    - Two empty CD Cases (Russian) (Box 12)
    - Stone Breath, DVD-1857 (Box 12)
      A Dream of You in the Garden of Gethsemane
    - Moth Masque, DVD-1858 (Box 12)
      Unfinished/Not Final Version
    - Charli XCX, CD-3232 (Box 21)
      Stay Away
    - Suchthaus, CD-3233 (Box 21)
      The Dark Side and the Bright Side
    - Skitliv, CD-3234 (Box 21)
      Demo
  - Subseries VI c. Records (David Tibet Groups)
    - Current 93
      - A Visit to Dogland, SR-9849 (Box 13)
      - Calling for Vanished Faces/Virgin Mary, SR-9850 (Box 14)
        Current 93/Antony and the Johnsons
      - Cerne 004, SR-9862 (Box 14)
        Current 93/Sol Invictus
      - Faust, SR-10327, SR-10334 (Box 30)
        master
      - Forms of Silence, SR-9851 (Box 13)
      - Holy Holy Holy (For Dusa), SR-9852 (Box 13)
      - I Have A Special Plan, SR-10332-10333 (Box 30)
      - Immortal Bird/Cripple and the Starfish, SR-9855 (Box 14)
      - Myths 4: Sinople Twilight in CaatalHuyuk, SR-9856 (Box 13)
        Current 93 and others
      - No Hiding From the Blackbird/The Burial of the Sardine, SR-9859-9860 (Box 14)
        Current 93/Nurse With Wound
      - No Hiding From the Blackbird/The Burial of the Sardine, SR-9919 (Box 14)
      - Ohrenschrauben, SR-9853 (Box 13)
      - She is Dead and All Fall Down/God Has Three Faces and Wood Has No Name, SR-9854 (Box 14)
      - Sleep Has His House, SR-9857-9858 (Box 14)
        2 copies
      - Sleep Has His House, SR-10329-10331 (Box 30)
      - Soft Black Stars, SR-10328 (Box 30)
      - Sveinbjorn Beinsteinsson "Edda", SR-9925 (Box 15)
      - Time Stands Still/Scrambled Egg Rebellion in the Smegma Dept, SR-9861 (Box 14)
    - Death in June
      - 93 Dead Sunwheels, SR-9863 (Box 13)
      - Brown Book, SR-9927 (Box 15)
      - But, What Ends When The Symbols Shatter?, SR-9864 (Box 13)
      - Cathedral of Tears, SR-9865 (Box 13)
      - Flowers of Autumn, SR-9866 (Box 13)
      - Live in Japan, SR-9867 (Box 13)
      - "Nada!", SR-9868 (Box 13)
      - Night and Fog, SR-9869 (Box 13)
      - Occidental Martyr, SR-9926 (Box 15)
      - Paradise Rising, SR-9870 (Box 13)
      - Rose Clouds of Holocaust, SR-9871 (Box 13)
      - She Said Destroy, SR-9872 (Box 14)
      - Sun Dogs, SR-9873 (Box 14)
      - To Drown A Rose, SR-9874 (Box 13)
      - The World That Summer, SR-9928 (Box 15)
    - Nurse with Wound
      - Nurse With Wound Live, SR-9875 (Box 13)
      - Alas the Madonna does not Function, SR-9876 (Box 13)
      - Alice the Goon, SR-9877-9878 (Box 13)
      - Alien, SR-9879 (Box 14)
      - Angry Eelectric Finger, SR-9880 (Box 13)
        Nurse With Wound/irr.app. (ext.)
      - Angry Eelectric Finger 1, SR-9881 (Box 13)
      - Angry Eelectric Finger 3, SR-9882 (Box 13)
      - Automating Volume 1, SR-9883 (Box 13)
      - Automating Volume 2, SR-9884 (Box 13)
      - An Awkward Pause, SR-9885 (Box 13)
      - The Bacteria Magnet, SR-9886 (Box 13)
      - Brained by Falling Masonry, SR-9887 (Box 13)
      - Chance Meeting Of Nurse With Wound And Unveiled On Charlottenborg, SR-9888 (Box 13)
        Nurse With Wound/Unveiled
      - Chance Meeting on a Dissecting Table of A Sewing Machine and an Umbrella, SR-9889 (Box 13)
      - Cooloorta Moon, SR-9890 (Box 13)
      - Could you Walk on the Waters, SR-9921 (Box 15)
        Nurse With Wound and others
      - Creakiness/Firemoon, SR-9891 (Box 13)
        Nurse With Wound/Spasm
      - Crumbduck, SR-9914 (Box 15)
        Nurse With Wound/Stereolab
      - Drunk with the Old Man of the Mountains, SR-9892 (Box 13)
      - Four Years in 30 Seconds, SR-9893 (Box 13)
      - Gyllenskold/Brained, SR-9894 (Box 13)
      - Gyllenskold, Geijerstam and I at Rydberg's, SR-9895 (Box 13)
      - Homotopy to Marie, SR-9896 (Box 13)
      - Insect and Individuals, SR-9897 (Box 13)
      - L'age d'or, SR-9898 (Box 13)
      - Masse Mensch, SR-9899 (Box 13)
      - Merzbild Schwet, SR-9900 (Box 13)
      - A Missing Sense/Rasa, SR-9901 (Box 13)
        Nurse With Wound/Organum
      - MTT Mauro Teho Teardo, SR-9923 (Box 15)
      - Ostranenie, SR-9902 (Box 13)
      - Papal Ejaculations, SR-9920 (Box 14)
        Nurse With Wound/Current 93
      - Psilotripitaka, SR-9903 (Box 15)
      - The Second Coming…, SR-9922 (Box 15)
      - Second Pirate Session, SR-9904 (Box 15)
      - She and Me Fall Together in Free Death, SR-9905 (Box 15)
      - Simple Headphone Mind, SR-9906 (Box 15)
      - Sinister Senile E.P., SR-9907 (Box 14)
      - The Sisters of Pataphysics, SR-9908 (Box 15)
      - Soliloquy for Lilith, SR-9909 (Box 15)
      - Soliloquy for Lilith, SR-9910 (Box 15)
      - Spiral Insana, SR-9911 (Box 15)
      - Soresucker, SR-9912 (Box 15)
      - Steel Dream March of the Metalmen, SR-9913 (Box 14)
      - Sylvie and Babs, SR-9924 (Box 15)
      - Thunder Perfect Mind, SR-9915 (Box 15)
      - The Termite Queen, SR-9916 (Box 14)
      - The Termite Queen, SR-9917 (Box 14)
      - To the Quiet Man from a Tiny Girl, SR-9918 (Box 15)
  - Subseries VI d. Records (Other)
    - 7 Year Rabbit Cycle, SR-10201 (Box 22)
      Wind Machines
    - 23 Skidoo, SR-10281 (Box 24)
    - 150 Muderous Passions, SR-10169 (Box 20)
      150 Muderous Passions
    - 200 Years, SR-9929 (Box 15)
      200 Years
    - Acca, SR-9930 (Box 15)
      [Title Unknown]
    - Aethenor, SR-9931 (Box 15)
    - Aethenor, SR-9932 (Box 15)
      Deep in Ocean Sunk the Lamp of Light
    - David Allen's Gong, SR-9933 (Box 15)
      Magick Brother
    - Alu, SR-9934 (Box 14)
      Bitte Warten Sie!
    - Alu, SR-9935 (Box 15)
      Ungesunde Traumbilder
    - Alu, SR-9936 (Box 15)
      Light
    - Alu, SR-9937 (Box 15)
      Alu's riskantes Experiment
    - Anderson, Marisa, SR-9938 (Box 15)
      The Golden Hour
    - Antony and the Johnsons, SR-9939 (Box 15)
      Hope There's Someone
    - Arian Sample, SR-9940 (Box 15)
      Hogs on Ice
    - The Aryan Aquarians, SR-9941 (Box 15)
      Meet Their Waterloo
    - Asbestos Death, SR-9942 (Box 14)
      Unclean
    - Asbestos Death, SR-9943 (Box 14)
      Dejection
    - aTelecine, SR-9944 (Box 14)
      a Vigiliant Carpark
    - August Born, SR-9945 (Box 15)
      August Born
    - Backworld, SR-9946 (Box 14)
      The Tide
    - Badget Lore, SR-9947 (Box 15)
      Badget Lore
    - Banhart, Devendra, SR-9948 (Box 15)
      Oh Me Oh My
    - Banhart, Devendra, SR-9949 (Box 14)
      Rejoicing in the Hands
    - Banhart, Devendra, SR-9950 (Box 14)
      A Sight to Behold/Be Kind
    - Banhart, Devendra, SR-9951 (Box 14)
      Little Yellow Spider
    - Basinski, William, SR-9952 (Box 16)
      Short Wave Pieces
    - Basinski, William, SR-9953 (Box 16)
      A Red Score in Tile
    - Beggar's Opera, SR-9954 (Box 16)
      Act One
    - The Bevis Frond, SR-9955 (Box 16)
      New River Head
    - The Bevis Frond, SR-9956 (Box 16)
      Son of Walter
    - Blackshaw, James, SR-9957 (Box 16)
      Holly EP
    - Blake, Karl, SR-9958 (Box 16)
      Thye Prehensile Tales
    - Blank Dogs, SR-9959 (Box 16)
      Diana (The Herald)
    - Blood Ceremony, SR-9960 (Box 16)
      Blood Ceremony
    - The Blue Humans, SR-9961 (Box 16)
      Live in NY
    - Blue Sabbath Black Cheer, SR-9962 (Box 16)
      The Endless Blockade
    - Bobby Beausoleil, SR-9963 (Box 16)
      The Lucifer Rising Suite
    - Bobby Brown, SR-9964 (Box 16)
      The Enlightening Beam of Axonda
    - Bobby Brown, SR-9965 (Box 16)
      Bobby Brown Live
    - Bobby Brown, SR-9966 (Box 16)
      Prayers of a One Man Band
    - Bombay Ducks, SR-9967 (Box 16)
      Dance Music
    - Bonnie "Blue" Billy, SR-9968 (Box 14)
      Little Boy Blue
    - Boyd And Rose, SR-9969 (Box 14)
      Boyd And Rose
    - The Cairo Gang, SR-9970 (Box 16)
      Twyxt Wyrd
    - The Cairo Gang, SR-9971 (Box 14)
      Holy Clover
    - Carter, Tom, SR-9972 (Box 16)
      Root King
    - Carthy, Martin; Swarbuck, Dave, SR-9973 (Box 16)
      Prince Heathen
    - Cashmore, Michael, SR-9974 (Box 16)
      The Snow Abides
    - Celestrial Communication Orchestra, SR-9975 (Box 16)
      Desert Mirage
    - Chalk, Andrew, SR-9976 (Box 16)
    - Chalk, Andrew, SR-9977 (Box 16)
      Yang-Tul
    - Chalk, Andrew; Toniutti, Giancarlo, SR-9978 (Box 16)
      Tahta Tarla
    - Chalk, Andrew, SR-9979 (Box 16)
      Over the Edges
    - Chalk, Andrew; Heemann; Duncan, SR-9980 (Box 14)
      The Eldaland-Vargaland National Anthem/Old Hive
    - Charalambides, SR-9981 (Box 16)
      Increase
    - Charalambides, SR-9982 (Box 16)
      Historic 6th Ward
    - Children's Hospital, SR-9983 (Box 16)
      Alone Together
    - Chrome, SR-9984 (Box 16)
      3rd From The Sun
    - Chrome, SR-9985 (Box 16)
      Alien Soundtracks
    - Chrome, SR-9986 (Box 16)
      Alien Soundtracks II
    - Chrome, SR-9987 (Box 16)
      Blood on the Moon
    - Chrome, SR-9988 (Box 16)
      Chromosome Damage
    - Chrome, SR-9989 (Box 16)
      The Chronicles I
    - Chrome, SR-9990 (Box 16)
      The Chronicles II
    - Chrome, SR-9991 (Box 17)
      Dreaming in Sequence
    - Chrome, SR-9992 (Box 17)
      Eternity
    - Chrome, SR-9993 (Box 17)
      Half Machine Lip Moves
    - Chrome, SR-9994 (Box 17)
      Into the Eyes of the Zombie King
    - Chrome, SR-9995 (Box 17)
    - Chrome, SR-9996 (Box 17)
      Liquid Forest
    - Chrome, SR-9997 (Box 17)
      Live in Germany
    - Chrome, SR-9998 (Box 17)
      The Lyon Concert
    - Chrome, SR-9999 (Box 17)
      Man's Ruin Records
    - Chrome, SR-10000 (Box 14)
      New Age
    - Chrome, SR-10001 (Box 17)
      Read Only Memory
    - Chrome, SR-10002 (Box 17)
      Red Exposure
    - Chrome, SR-10003 (Box 17)
    - Chrome, SR-10004 (Box 17)
      The Visitation
    - Chrome, SR-10005 (Box 17)
      Limited Edition box, Subterranean Siren
    - Chrystal Belle Scrodd, SR-10006 (Box 17)
      Belle de Jour
    - Chrystal Belle Scrodd, SR-10007 (Box 17)
      The Inevitable
    - Circle of Ouroborus, SR-10008 (Box 17)
      Veneration
    - Circle, SR-10009 (Box 14)
      Ghatarian
    - Coffee, SR-10010 (Box 17)
      Hex Vex and the Lavender Mink
    - Coleclough, Jonathan; Chalk, Andrew, SR-10011 (Box 17)
      Sumac
    - Comets on Fire, SR-10012 (Box 17)
    - Comets on Fire, SR-10013 (Box 17)
      Field Recordings from the Sun
    - Comets on Fire and Major Stars, SR-10014 (Box 17)
      Live in Europa
    - Compound Eye, SR-10015 (Box 17)
      Origin of Silence
    - Connelly, Chris, SR-10016 (Box 17)
      Pentland Firthowl
    - Corsano, Chris; Chasny, Ben, SR-10017 (Box 17)
      Roaratorio
    - Creed, Helios, SR-10018 (Box 17)
      Boxing the Clown
    - Creed, Helios, SR-10019 (Box 17)
      Lactating Purple
    - Creed, Helios, SR-10020 (Box 14)
      Nothing Wrong b/w The Sky
    - Cromagnon, SR-10021 (Box 17)
      Orgasm
    - Crowley, Aleister, SR-10022 (Box 17)
      Hastings Archive, Goetia 666
    - Cruise, Julie, SR-10023 (Box 17)
      Floating Into the Night9
    - Diagonal, SR-10024 (Box 17)
      Diagonal
    - Directing Hand, SR-10025 (Box 17)
      What Put the Blood
    - Double Leopards, SR-10026 (Box 17)
      Halve Moon
    - Doyle, Arthur, SR-10027 (Box 14)
      Egg Head
    - Doyle, Arthur, SR-10028 (Box 17)
      Live In Japan
    - Doyle, Arthur, SR-10029 (Box 17)
    - Doyle, Arthur, SR-10030 (Box 14)
      Love Ship/Mama Love Papa Love
    - Doyle, Arthur, SR-10031 (Box 14)
    - Doyle, Arthur; Drake, Hamid, SR-10032 (Box 17)
      Your Spirit is Calling
    - Arthur Doyle Electro-Acoustic Ensemble, SR-10033 (Box 17)
      Conspiracy Nation
    - Doyle, Arthur, SR-10034 (Box 17)
      Plays and Sings from the Songbook
    - Doyle, Arthur, SR-10035 (Box 18)
      Plays More Alabama Feeling
    - Arthur Doyle Electro-Acoustic Ensemble, SR-10036 (Box 18)
      Plays the African Love Call
    - Doyle, Arthur, SR-10037 (Box 18)
      No More Crazy Women
    - Dransfield, Robin, SR-10038 (Box 18)
      Tidewave
    - Dransfield, Robin, SR-10039 (Box 18)
      The Tiddler's Wreath
    - Eater, SR-10040 (Box 18)
      Lock it Up
    - Erickson, Roky, SR-10041 (Box 14)
      Two-Twisted Tales
    - Exhumed Corpse, SR-10042 (Box 18)
      The Crows Fly, The Wolves Fly…
    - Exhumed Corpse, SR-10043 (Box 18)
      Pray for Death
    - Exmagma, SR-10044 (Box 18)
      Exmagma
    - Ferial Confine, SR-10045 (Box 18)
      The Full Use of Nothing
    - G.F. Fitz-Gerald, SR-10046 (Box 18)
      Mouseproof
    - Fry, Mark, SR-10047 (Box 18)
      Dreaming With Alice
    - Genesis, SR-10048 (Box 18)
      Live
    - Gerrard, Denny, SR-10049 (Box 18)
      Sinister Morning
    - Ginnungagap, SR-10050 (Box 18)
      1000% Downer
    - Ginnungagap, SR-10051 (Box 18)
      Remeindre
    - Ginnungagap, SR-10052 (Box 18)
      Crashed Like Wretched Moth
    - Giombini, Mark; Barbarino, Enzo, SR-10053 (Box 18)
      Trans Vita Express
    - Giombini, Marcello, SR-10054 (Box 18)
      Io Contrero' Pace
    - Gold Cosmos, SR-10055 (Box 18)
      Gold Cosmos
    - Goldberg, SR-10056 (Box 18)
      Misty Flats
    - Greene, Burtion, SR-10057 (Box 18)
      Celesphere
    - Grey, Rudolph, SR-10058 (Box 18)
      Transfixed
    - Gurdjieff; De Hartmann, SR-10059 (Box 18)
      Gurdjieff/De Hartmann
    - Guru Guru; Uli Trepte, SR-10060 (Box 18)
      Hot On Spot/Inbetween
    - Gyllenskold, Geijertam and Friends, SR-10061 (Box 18)
    - Hiagh, Robert, SR-10062 (Box 18)
      Valentine Out of Season
    - Hansson, Bo, SR-10063 (Box 18)
      In de Ban Van de Ring
    - Hastings of Malawi, SR-10064 (Box 18)
      Vibrant Stapler Obscures Characteristic Growth
    - Heemann, Christoph; Martin, Andreas, SR-10065 (Box 18)
    - Heemann, Christoph, SR-10066 (Box 18)
      Magnetic Tape Splicing
    - Heemann, Christoph; Chalk, Andrew, SR-10067 (Box 18)
      The Mirror of the Sea
    - Heemann, Christoph; Chalk, Andrew, SR-10068 (Box 14)
      Die Stadt
    - Heemann, Christoph, SR-10069 (Box 14)
      Retrace
    - Heemann, Christoph, SR-10070 (Box 14)
    - Heemann, Christoph, SR-10071 (Box 18)
      Uber Den Umgang Mit Umgebung und Andere Versuche
    - High Tide, SR-10072 (Box 18)
      Precious Cargo
    - Hirsche Nicht Aufs Sofa, SR-10073 (Box 18)
      Ach, Dieser Bart
    - Hirsche Nicht Aufs Sofa, SR-10074 (Box 18)
    - Hirsche Nicht Aufs Sofa, SR-10075 (Box 18)
      Face to Face
    - Hirsche Nicht Aufs Sofa, SR-10076 (Box 18)
      The Book of Dingenskirchen
    - Hirsche Nicht Aufs Sofa, SR-10077 (Box 18)
      Im Schatten Der Mohre
    - Hirsche Nicht Aufs Sofa, SR-10078 (Box 18)
      Melchior